Privacy Notice
==============

##### v2.0 February 2023

Contents
--------

* What information do we collect about you?
* How will we use this information?  
    
* Storage and safeguards
* Marketing
* Cookies and tracking
* Your Rights
* Links to other websites
* Changes to our Privacy Notice
* How to contact us

What information do we collect about you?
-----------------------------------------

We collect information about you for the purposes of entering into a contract with you for our Shopiago services. The information we collect is your full name and business contact details (email and phone number). We need this information as it is necessary to perform our contract with you or the organisation you represent.

We also collect information about you when you contact us with an enquiry or to report a problem about our services or our site. This includes when you make an enquiry via our website using the chat function, (we use HubSpot Live Chat). **This is in our legitimate business interests.**

We also collect:

* a record of business contacts of our suppliers, advisers and agents and their contact information in order to manage our commercial relationship with that third party and perform contractual obligations (i.e. it is necessary for us to perform a contract); 
* a record of contacts from any regulators linked to our industry, together with their contact information, in order to comply with a legal obligation; and
* a record of prospective business contacts. This is in our legitimate business interests (i.e. we have a justifiable reason for processing information in this way).

If you do not provide certain personal information, we may not be able to assist with your enquiry or perform our contract with you.

We also retain certain information about you when you use our website which is set out in more detail below.

Where you are an employee of one of our customers, we may process your name, email address, phone number and place of work under our contract with our customer and we may ask you if we can send you marketing emails about our services that we think may be of interest to you. We will only ever do this where we have your consent.

Technical information we collect on our website

When you use our website we collect information about you and your device. This is technical information about your browser and operating system so that we can ensure adequate technical support for our website and ensure it is functioning properly on all operating systems/browsers. **This is within our legitimate business interests.**

We also collect general site usage data using cookies, local storage or tagging technology for the purposes of improving our website, personalising your visit and offering our services to you. We also collect information about the site you have clicked through from. We do this by using cookies to identify you and we seek your consent for any cookie that is not essential to the functioning of our website. This is explained in more detail below and in our Cookie Notice.

How will we use this information?
---------------------------------

As explained above, we use your personal information to improve our website and other products / services, and to offer our services to you. This includes working with partners and suppliers so that we can provide our services and website to you for example third party fulfilment providers and our development team based in Hungary. We also work with:

HubSpot – Our Central CRM system for all customer interactions

Below we also set out the lawful bases that we rely on for our processing activities.

Generally, we process your personal data so that we can perform our contract with you. 

Where we email or market to you about other products and services we will rely on either our legitimate business interests or consent.

We may also need to process your personal information in order to comply with our own legal and regulatory obligations, and in those cases that obligation will be our lawful basis for doing so.

We may also need to share your personal data with a third party if that third party is considering investing in us or acquiring all or part of our business. If we do so, we will ensure that appropriate security measures are in place. Our lawful basis for this is our legitimate business interests in seeking investment and growing our business.

Our Use of Social Media
-----------------------

We may work with social and business media platforms including Facebook, LinkedIn and Twitter to bring you targeted advertising about our services and improve your experience on our website. We will always seek your consent before we do this.

Storage and safeguards and how long we store your data for
----------------------------------------------------------

Under data protection legislation, we are legally required to inform you where your personal data is stored and how it is protected. As part of due diligence in our usage of third parties, we ensure they follow the highest standards of data protection and security.

This website is hosted with Google Cloud, who store data in the UK.

Business and charity contact Personal Data is stored in Hubspot found here. HubSpot store data in the US.

We always make sure we have proper safeguards in place to protect your data and we will only transfer your personal data to a country or international organisation outside the UK where:

* the UK government has decided the particular country or international organisation ensures an adequate level of protection of personal data (known as an ‘adequacy decision’);
* there are appropriate safeguards in place, together with enforceable rights and effective legal remedies for data subjects; or
* a specific exception applies under data protection law

If you would like further information about data transferred outside the UK, please contact us.

Personal information is collected and used for the reasons set out above, and shall not be stored for longer than necessary for those purposes.

Generally, where your organisation enters into a contract with us, we store your personal information for the period of the contract, plus an additional seven years. Where you do not sign up for an account or otherwise use our website, including reporting any problems or asking us any questions, we store your personal information for no more than two years. Where we store your data for marketing purposes, we typically store data for 2 years for that purpose. The Google Analytics cookie typically expires after two years or when you clear your cache.

Marketing
---------

We may send you information about products and services of ours or of other companies in the World of Books Ltd Group which we believe may be of interest and will rely on either our legitimate business interests or consent to do so. We partner with HubSpot to provide these services for us.

If you are an employee of one of our customers, we will always seek your consent to send you any marketing materials.

You may opt out from marketing communications at any time. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes and you can always alter your marketing preferences in our Preference Centre.

We will not share your information for marketing purposes with any of our Group companies unless you tell us we can.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, you can also email us at:

help@shopiago.com

Cookies and tracking
--------------------

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet usage information and track visitor behaviour. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and provide reports on usage, such as for website analytics purposes.

We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users which may be relevant to offering our products to you. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.

To see further details, including on the use of third party cookies, and to learn how you can manage your cookie preferences, please refer to our Cookie Notice.

We rely on the lawful basis of consent to process your personal information using non-essential cookies or other similar technologies. We rely on the lawful basis of legitimate business interests for processing your personal information using essential cookies.

We may also utilise tracking technology on the web properties, for analytics, marketing or performance tracking. We use this to improve and enhance our communication with you or the products / services we offer. We use a tracking pixel provided by Google that tracks how you interact with our site. You may then receive targeted advertising on other websites or Google platforms. Where we do this we always seek your express consent.

Please see further details in our Cookie Notice on how you can manage your cookie preferences and how you can set your browser to not accept cookies. However, in this case please note that some of our site features may not function as a result.

Your Rights
-----------

Under data protection law, you have the following rights:

* **Request access** to your personal information (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it. You may also do this yourself through the My Account dashboard (if you are a registered customer).
* **Request correction** of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
* **Request erasure** of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
* **Object to processing** of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
* **Request the restriction** of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
* **Request the transfer** of your personal information to another party.

The above rights are not absolute, and in certain circumstances we may refuse to comply with your request to exercise them. In those cases we will inform you of our refusal and our reasons for it. In some circumstances, we may also charge you for our cost of complying with your rights, but only where permitted to do so by law (and where we have given you notice that we will do so).

If you what to contact us about how we use your information or in the unlikely event you have a complaint, please email us at: data@worldofbooks.com

Links to other websites
-----------------------

Our website contains links to other websites, this privacy notice only applies to this web property, if you navigate away to other websites this notice is no longer applicable.

Changes to our Privacy Notice
-----------------------------

From time to time, we may update our privacy notice in order to remain compliant with data protection legislation. We will do our best to notify our customers and contacts, but please refer to this periodically for the latest updates. You can always find the latest version of this notice on our website.

How to contact us
-----------------

Mailing Address: Shopiago, part of the World of Books Group, Mulberry House, Woods Way, Goring-by-Sea, West Sussex, BN12 4QY, United Kingdom

Telephone: 01903 507 544

Email: Email information data@worldofbooks.com

Shopiago
--------

World of Books Group
--------------------

Sign up to our monthly newsletter!
----------------------------------
